datbootcamp.com 2019-03-03

# Privacy Policy | DAT Bootcamp

Date Effective: 05-23-2018

At Bootcamp Prep, LLC, (“Bootcamp Prep”,) Bootcamp Prep is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. Please take some time to read this Privacy Policy so You will understand how Bootcamp Prep treats the information it collects from its users (“You”, “Your”, “User”). Please also understand that by accessing Bootcamp Prep you are expressly consenting to the Terms and Policies set out in this Privacy Policy.

 **1.1 Scope**

This Privacy Policy details how Bootcamp Prep collects, handles, uses, and disposes of the information that it collects from its Users. The Terms and Policies contained herein apply to any time a user accesses Bootcamp Prep’s website (“Bootcamp Prep”), purchases a service from Bootcamp Prep, or sends an email (including other forms of communication) to Bootcamp Prep or its officers, agents or employees.

 **2.1 Why Bootcamp Prep collects your personal information**

In general, Bootcamp Prep collects and uses information about You, its User, in order to more effectively provide services to You, including but not limited to services You purchase, membership benefits, and personal account management and administration. Bootcamp Prep does not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties. Bootcamp Prep only discloses Your personal information to third parties where necessary to perform the service you have purchased from Bootcamp Prep.

 **3.1 What information does Bootcamp Prep Collect from You**

In order to provide the highest quality of service, Bootcamp Prep collects a variety of data from a variety of sources. The information Bootcamp Prep collects can be broken down into three (3) general categories: generic or non-service specific data, service specific data, and automatically collected Internet use data. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

 **3.2 Generic, non-service specific data**

When You visit Bootcamp Prep, Bootcamp Prep may record information about Your use of the site, including searches that you run, and which areas of the site you access. If you create a user profile, Bootcamp Prep will record any information which you submit in connection with the profile creation process. This information will be retained for the time during which your profile remains active. Bootcamp Prep also collects and stores any correspondences you make to Us, including but not limited to mail, e-mails, facsimile, telephone, and suggestions submitted through Bootcamp Prep. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

 **3.3 Service Specific Information**

If the event that You purchase a service offered by Bootcamp Prep, You may be asked to provide Bootcamp Prep with a considerable amount of personal data through the completion of a detailed questionnaire. This information includes but is not limited to your name, phone numbers, identification numbers (such as driver’s license number, social security number), birth information, addresses, criminal history, employment history, affiliations and social media use and usernames. Bootcamp Prep collects this information solely to further the performance of the associated service.

Bootcamp Prep uses this information to search for information pertaining to You on the internet, in public records, social media, blogs, and other sources. Bootcamp Prep may use third parties in efforts to search for information pertaining to you more comprehensively. This information is collected only in furtherance of performing the service You have purchased. Bootcamp Prep does not sell, rent, lease, or license this information out to any third parties. Furthermore, Bootcamp Prep does not disclose this information to any third parties for marketing or advertising purposes, and disclosure is based solely on furthering the performance of services for You.

 **3.4 Automatically Collected Internet Use Data**

IP and URL addresses  
Like many other Web sites, Bootcamp Prep collects information about its users’ utilization and navigation of our Site. This information allows Bootcamp Prep to better suit Your needs. Bootcamp Prep may also use Your IP address to help diagnose problems with its server and to administer its Site, analyze trends, track visitor movements, and gather broad demographic information that assists Bootcamp Prep in identifying User preferences. Bootcamp Prep also records the most recent login time of its User accounts.

Cookies  
In efforts to provide You with exceptional service, Bootcamp Prep may use cookies to store and help track information about You. Cookies are small data packages that are sent to Your browser from a web server and stored on Your computer’s hard drive. Bootcamp Prep uses cookies to help You navigate our sites during Your visits. Cookies allow Bootcamp Prep to recognize You and save Your preferences and settings, in order to provide an easier to use and more convenient experience.

Google Analytics  
Bootcamp Prep uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics also uses Cookies to help Bootcamp Prep analyze how Users use the site. The information collected by these cookies (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating Your use of Bootcamp Prep, compiling reports on website activity, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate Your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on Your browser, however please note that if You do this You may not be able to enjoy all the features of Bootcamp Prep.

 **4.1 What Bootcamp Prep does with the information it collects**

Generic, non-service specific information  
Bootcamp Prep uses generic, non-service specific information to administer and maintain its website, Bootcamp Prep, as well as to improve its functionality and convenience to its Users. User Account information is used to manage and maintain Your profile on Bootcamp Prep. Bootcamp Prep will not sell, lease, license, or rent any of this information. It will solely be used by Bootcamp Prep and will not be disclosed to third parties for any advertising, marketing or data aggregating purposes.

Service Specific data  
Bootcamp Prep uses service specific data solely in furtherance of performing the service that it was collected on behalf of. Bootcamp Prep will not sell, rent, or lease, this data to any third parties. Disclosure of this data to trusted third parties may be necessary in order to perform the service You have purchased. Bootcamp Prep will only disclose Your personal information to third parties to the extent required to further the service you have purchased.

Automatically Collected Internet Use data  
Bootcamp Prep uses this data in order to administer and maintain its website (www.DATBootcamp.com), as well as analyze its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use, and improve its functionality and convenience to its Users.

 **5.1 How do we protect your information**

Bootcamp Prep has implemented appropriate security measures to help protect Your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For the duration of time that Bootcamp Prep stores Your personal information, the data will be located on a secure database with restricted access. Please understand, Bootcamp Prep takes reasonable and appropriate precautions in ensuring Your personal data is keep safe and secure, however, we cannot, and do not guarantee that an unauthorized person will never be able to access Your personal information.

 **6.1 When do we disclose Your Personal Information**

As mentioned above, Bootcamp Prep does not sell, lease, license, or rent your personal information to any third party. Bootcamp Prep will only disclose your information to trusted third parties in connection with the performance of a service You have purchased, and only to the extent necessary to adequately perform the service you have purchased. Bootcamp Prep may also disclose Your information, as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another company or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if Bootcamp Prep believes in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.

Your access to some areas of Bootcamp Prep, including your profile and the members area will be username and password protected by a username and password combination that You select. Bootcamp Prep requires that you do not share your password or username with anyone in its User Agreement. Unauthorized access to your personal information may result from Your sharing of this information with other people or third parties.

 **6.2 Merger or Transfer**

Should we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information.

 **7.1 How can you Correct, Amend, Retrieve, or delete information, or modify your personal preferences**

Bootcamp Prep permits You to cancel your account or update your preferences at any time. Bootcamp Prep may send you promotional material and special offers from time to time. If you do not want to receive this information about Bootcamp Prep’s products or services, please update Your account preferences (where available), check the appropriate box when registering, or select the “unsubscribe” option within the e-mails that you receive from Bootcamp Prep. If you cancel you user account, your information and settings will be purged from our data banks in our next scheduled data purge.

 **8.1 Policy updates**

If Bootcamp Prep’s Privacy Policy changes in any significant way, the new version will be posted on Bootcamp Prep. The Current version is effective as of 05-23-2018.

 **9.1 Questions**

If you have any question regarding Bootcamp Prep’s Privacy Policy please contact us at ari@DATBootcamp.com.
